## JOOSEP KÕIVISTIK SENIOR FRONTEND ENGINEER

(+45) 50302356 jokoivi@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/jokoivi

#### **Profile**



I'm an enthusiastic senior frontend engineer who's specialised in building complex SaaS web applications based on the Angular framework.

I love working in large teams where there is a lot of interaction, code reviews, retros, good standards and everyone contributing and learning from one-another. I prefer an environment where there is a lot of collaboration between tech and product in order to deliver the best possible solutions.

### **Technical**

#### **BASE SKILLS**

	ı	Years
HTML / SCSS		16
Javascript		14
Typescript		4
Angular		4
Redux / Ngrx		4
AngularJS		8
RESTful APIs		

## **EXPERIENCE**

Building complex applications
Team work
Leading projects
Planning & Grooming
UI & UX design
Mentoring juniors
Responsive design

## **TOOLS**

Jira / Confluence
Github / Gitlab
Photoshop
Windows
scrum
WSL (ubuntu)

## Experience

## Kahoot! / Actimo Senior Frontend Engineer

2020 - Now

In 2020, Actimo was acquired by kahoot with the goal of being able to put more resources into growing their corporate solutions.

 I still continued working on the 'Actimo' platform, so i have rather summarised all the highlights in the next section



kahoot.com

Actimo 2017 - 2020

#### Senior Frontend Engineer

A platform which allows companies to create their own branded employee apps for onboarding, communication, training, employee-manager evaluations and for some social aspects.

- During my time at actimo, the whole platform has grown immensely both in terms of the
  overall feature offerings but also the architecture, scalability and code quality. Having always
  been either the only, or one of the two senior frontenders, I have played an integral role on
  most of the projects over the past 5 years. The most notable examples being:
  - Rebuilding the whole end-user facing app from scratch using Angular and NgRx
  - Gradual re-build of the editor-facing app (angularJS + Angular hybrid where all new development was in Angular and the most relevant pages, components and architecture were fully converted one project at the time)
  - o Actimo Academy feature More info
  - The Editor feature Complete rebuild & revamp of the way we handled our user generated content, combining 6+ different page sets and concepts into a single unified pattern. - More info
  - Pulse & One-on-one manager / employee evaluation features
  - o Social wall feature kind of like Facebook groups.
  - o Dashboards feature Global stats page
  - Employee profiles
- · Countless of smaller features and enhancements
- Onboarding and mentoring 2 junior developers
- Running frontend workgroups, documenting processes and making sure we follow them.
- Helping with recruiting scouting for candidates, doing interviews and reviewing tests.



actimo.com

Tame Lead Frontend Developer 2016 - 2017

At the time a very fresh startup working on an all in one platform for organising events

- Working on a react and nodejs based SaaS tool for organizing events
- · Working alongside the lead designer to come up with optimal ui/ux solutions / patterns
- Creating a modular and reusable component base



tame.events

## Agillic Aps Frontend Developer

Omnichannel marketing automation platform

- Designing and developing the user-interface for their "Match" product line / MVC based AngularJS web application
- Rewriting of a complex B2B web app "Dialogue" which was originally built upon now deprecated Flex framework. The new app was to be a proper modular, responsive / multi device capable HTML5 / AngularJS based MVC app using simple REST/json endpoints
- communicating requests for api's and their model formats with the backend team in ukraine
- · Enhancing & improving the existing UI



agillic.com

# Hapti.co (io-interactive's subsidiary) Junior Frontend Developer

2012 - 2013

A game studio which worked on a project called "Gameglobe" - a next gen browser game/portal driven by user generated content.

- Frontend implementation for new features using jquery & html
- · backend implementation using python/django
- · Ensuring cross browser compatability
- · Modifying designs in photoshop to be responsive
- Finding bugs and improving the existing UI
- · Improving and cleaning the existing codebase



tiny.one/gameglobe

## Svejstrup & Lyng ApS Lead Frontend Developer

2011 - 2012

A tiny architecture bureau

- · Architectural 3D visualization.
- Creating and maintaining websites for various projects, sub-companies and assosiates.
- · Designing logos, business cards.

## Estonian defense forces

mandatory service of 9 months

Webox I/S

2008 - 2009

web developer

A web design company i created with a few friends on the side of our studies

· Creating simple home pages.

## Education

## Odder Højskole

2011 - 2011

6 months course focusing on:

- Drawing
- Painting
- · creativity and form
- Photography

## **Business Academy Arhus**

2007 - 2009

AP degree in multimedia design and communication

- · Communication and presentation
- Design and visualization
- Interaction development
- Digital marketing

## Otepää Gymnasium

1994 - 2007

12 grade education

#### Additional

#### **PERSONAL**

#### **LANGUAGES**

#### **HOBBIES**

Crafting / DIY

Location: Cph, Denmark

Nationality: Estonian

Born: Nov 23, 1987

Web: koivistik.com

Estonian | native
English | Fluent

Danish | Limited (module 4)

Photography / Videography

Art projects